So I'm going to tell you now, this is a 10 minute video, but I would really appreciate
if you would watch it to its conclusion.
So I woke up to this little gem.
Apparently I'm promoting Hamas to my followers, to my 2.1 million followers.
These people are dangerous.
You know, this, this Zionist or these Zionists are dangerous.
The efforts through which they go to try to silence people who ask questions, who deem
people who aren't them as human, namely Palestinians.
I'm going to play this clip for y'all so you can see me vociferously defending Hamas.
Oh man, what a world we're in.
What a world.
And they're, they're trying to say that, you know, Hamas as a culture is of terrorism.
It is a bad apples.
And I think that from what we're seeing, that simply is just not a fair assessment.
And even if there were a Hamasian that were a bad apple, that doesn't speak to the whole
organization.
We like to give bad apple status to the actual oppressor, even though they're oppressing.
But ultimately, like Hamas has been presented as this like big bad wolf.
They're not considered people.
They're not talked about as people.
They're talked about as like this one entity.
And that's by design.
It's by design.
They're, they're this mysterious entity that is coming for all of us.
That's by design.
But we all know who's the actual entity coming for all of us.
And even if Hamas was, they don't got the, they don't got the reins.
They don't got the tools.
They don't got, they don't, they don't got the bombs.
They don't got the planes.
They don't got the drones.
They don't got it.
You know who does though.
And since they started my video in the middle, let's just for the sake of, you know, context,
provide the beginning.
Hear me out.
So every, um, former Zionist says that what changed them was actually being in the West
Bank or being in Gaza or just being in the company of Palestinians and understanding their
story and hearing their story.
Is it possible that the reason we're seeing such, um, congenial responses between the hostages
and Hamas, is it possible that it's not because Hamas is still holding some of their family,
but that they have for the first time had a real interaction with Palestinians and actually
got to hear the reason for their cause, et cetera.
I'm just throwing that out there.
But I ask these questions because Hamas are people too, you know, and I don't know if the
whole bunch is, you know, sane or not, but I know that the whole bunch are the victims
of an oppressive apartheid regime.
And I know that when people like Marco Rubio and Netanyahu and the rest of these fools call
them animals, it makes it like, oh, they cannot be communicated with.
They don't have any human ability to interact.
And so that, that absolves them of the necessity to have to interact with them, which we all
know is a tactic to dehumanize.
I think it's also important though, to note that when you see IDF soldiers who come out
of the IDF and have had their minds shifted and changed, they are like, yeah, it's a culture
that you're a part of.
And I realized within that culture that I could not be myself as a good person within that culture.
I feel like for the first time in my life, the boundaries between good and bad that I learned
as a kid, and obviously I learned that I'm on the good side, I was broken.
I felt like I am the terrorist and my job was literally to scare people so they cannot
think about acting against the Israeli settlers or the Israeli military.
And that's a different thing.
You know, we talk about that with policing, you know, when people say, oh, it's just one
bad apple.
It's like, no, the culture is the bad apple.
And they're, they're trying to say that, you know, Hamas as a culture is of terrorism.
It is a bad apples.
And I think that from what we're seeing, that simply is just not a fair assessment.
And even if there were a Hamasian.
Okay, so now you get the full picture.
I digress.
Then there was very rich person, Bill Ackman, who also decided to chime in and said, in the
below video, Amanda vociferously defends Hamas.
10 points for Gryffindor.
That's actually a great word.
In this incredible ignorance, conscious avoidance of the truth or racism, I can't come up with
an alternative explanation.
A large proportion of the Hamas supporters on university campuses and elsewhere, like Amanda,
are members of the black community and or other people of color.
Why?
Some have argued that this is due to the diversity, equity, and inclusion movement, which delineates
the world in an oppressor slash oppressed framework.
Is that what does that?
In the DEI worldview, Jews are deemed to be white oppressors, even though many Jews, particularly
these in Israel, are not white and or don't identify as white.
Bill, if you would like to have a conversation about this, if you genuinely want to know the
answers to these questions, then we should set up a conversation and it should be public.
I have a master's degree in African-American studies.
I am more than happy to have an intellectual conversation to provide you with the understanding
that you seem to lack in grasping these concepts because it is important that people understand.
Um, I literally woke up and did these videos.
If you all would like to add in the comments some context for Bill Ackman, because I know
that I'm very fortunate to have a number of really well-learned, strongly compassionate
people that follow this page on Instagram, please drop it in the comments.
But again, I would love to invite Bill Ackman to have a public conversation around this topic.
There is a continued effort of division that is supported by willful ignorance, and that
is only challenged by direct addressing of the issue with facts.
And actually, while I have you, I just want to point out the fact that Zionism is racist.
The major problem of Israel is with the younger generation of the Black community.
Black Lives Matter starts there.
So, you know, they love that I'm a Black woman saying this.
They love that, right?
Because it's like, oh my God, how dare this negress speak of these others with any level of thoughtfulness?
And, um, I will say that they are wrong in any suggestion that labels me anti-Semitic.
And, you know, we are watching the efforts consistently to deem individuals who consider Hamas as anything other than what they deem them as, you know, a problem.
And I'm going to pop in here.
What exactly is promoting Hamas?
Like, are we waving Hamas flags?
Are we wearing Hamas shirts?
You know, are we, like, walking door-to-door with sign-ups, like, join Hamas for summer camp?
Because y'all are definitely waving Israeli flags while Israel is carrying out a genocide.
The existence of Hamas does not absolve Israel of its consistent crimes against humanity, no matter how many times they say so.
That the bombing and the Israeli military attacks on Gaza have officially restarted.